<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[The Internet Marketing Mom]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[The Internet Marketing Mom]]></description>
        <link>http://internetmarketing.mom/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Mar 2018 02:41:58 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="http://internetmarketing.mom/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Mar 2018 02:41:57 GMT</pubDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[7 Reasons Why To Become A Work-From-Home Mom]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/eb33a7bf-8fcc-4360-9707-4428cd34cdf1.jpg">,<h1><strong>7 Reasons Why To Become A Work-From-Home Mom</strong></h1>,<p>It’s been often said that “necessity is the mother of all inventions”. Which is true.</p>,<p>Thousands of women worldwide have found a challenge to keep a balance between a successful career and being a successful mom.</p>,<p>And when the time comes, thousands of women, too, have found some dismal when taking a decision on which path to take when it comes to both worlds.</p>,<p>Here are 7 ‘magical’ reasons why a woman would want to become a ‘work-from-home’ Mom.</p>,<p><strong>You will have more time for your kids.</strong></p>,<p>Becoming a work-from-home-mom means that you are definitely going to spend more time with them and become a more important part of their life. Although it might cut both ways, you are going to have the time to create more balance. Not all of the time will be for them, but you will definitely have more.</p>,<p>You will not miss any milestones like when they first make a childish-groundbreaking realization like when the pets do not brush their teeth with regular toothpaste or when they start speaking and mumbling those words like “Da-da” or “Mo-mmy”.</p>,<p><strong>Increase your income</strong></p>,<p><em>Isn’t saving money another form of increasing your income?</em> Take pen and paper and outline the benefits of investing more energy in your project and how much of a savings you are having from no-longer-necessary environmental costs of going out that often.</p>,<p><strong>Having the perfect balance for the ideal life</strong></p>,<p>Let’s be clear: We all want to be our own bosses, spend more time with our families and give them a better quality of life. If more time for you means more quality of life, then you got an ace with this one.</p>,<p><strong>More flexibility for your schedule</strong></p>,<p>Think about this: Have you ever had to ask your boss for permission to leave work earlier to pick one of your kids or visiting the infirmary?</p>,<p>With such flexibility, you will have an extended empowerment towards your schedule and timetables. Either at the beginning or at the end of the day, you will have the insight on how much power you have over your life.</p>,<p><strong>Have Additional Time</strong></p>,<p>One way or another, if you make the math on how much time you spend in round trips to pick up your kids at school and other earrings, you will realize on what a big deal of time you have lost in a simple routine.</p>,<p>Roll that over to days, weeks, months and years, still a great deal of time that you will save instead dedicating that time to the, with your work-from-home endeavor.</p>,<p><strong>Gaining more money as an independent than at office</strong></p>,<p>According to the <em><strong>World Economic Forum,</strong></em> in their <em><strong><a href="http://reports.weforum.org/global-gender-gap-report-2017/" title="Global Gender Gap Report 2017">Global Gender Gap Report 2017</a>, </strong></em>women are more often to work in industries where the wages are lower than men.</p>,<p>But, what happens when you work at home? You get to raise the bar for yourself. All of that income will be yours to keep and you can gain more opportunities to find one sweet hotspot that will make more money for you to keep.</p>,<p><strong>Dodge the office social distractions</strong></p>,<p>We all know that once in while is OK to go out with friends and have fun or some sort of distraction. But often happens that we cannot keep up to date with wo many invitations, meetings, dinners, and other social <em>rendez-vous </em>that take place at an office. Instead, you can just stay at home, watch a family movie with your children and have a heck lot of fun!</p>,<h3><strong>A few more hints</strong></h3>,<p>Why not doing both? More and more people are joining a work-from-home environment and looking forward to more freedom, flexibility, more income and a happier life.</p>,<p>Being a work-from-home mom may be a long-lasting desire and dream that wants to unfold. Get the signs from the universe. Follow your heart and your guts.</p>,<p>Present day advancements in technology and globalization will make this striving desire easier, joyful and challenging. Internet is a vast highway that will allow you to connect with more people, and more opportunitiesthan just being realizing other peoples’ dreams working for a company at an office.</p>,<p><em><strong>Note: If you are truly interested in finding options to become an independent-work-from-home-mom, you may want to check <a href="http://bit.ly/theinternetmarketingmom" title="Make Money From Home">this option</a>.</strong></em></p>,<p><em>As you may understand, we are a website that needs compensation to operate like any other website on the internet. We may receive consideration for our reviews but we are totally unbiased and do not accept paid reviews or fake reviews claiming to be something they are not. We are independently owned and the opinions expressed here are our own.Some of the links are affiliate links, meaning, at no additional cost to you, we will earn a commission if you click through and make a purchase.</em></p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/7adc8596-23ae-42cb-afd6-94cd8ee430ac.jpg">,<p><em>Notes: Images courtesy of picjumbo.com</em></p>]]></description>
            <link>http://internetmarketing.mom/7-reasons-why-a-mom-can-succeed-working-from-home/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">43e22acf-a04c-4fee-92d4-1dd3740c0ed1</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2018 20:23:31 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>